<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<quotes>
  <quote>Anonymous methods and anonymous types are really all called Jon Skeet. They just don&apos;t like to boast.</quote>
  <quote>Compatibility doesn&apos;t exist in Jon Skeet&apos;s dictionary. He can easily work in Microsoft Office in Linux on a Mac.</quote>
  <quote>Contrary to popular belief, there is enough Jon Skeetto go around...and then some.</quote>
  <quote>Donald Knuth wears a &quot;Jon Skeet is my Homeboy&quot; t-shirt to show off at parties.</quote>
  <quote>God didn&apos;t really create the world in six days, because Jon Skeet optimized it to one.</quote>
  <quote>God said: &apos;Let there be light,&apos; only so he could see what Jon Skeet was up to.</quote>
  <quote>Godzilla is a Japanese rendition of Jon&apos;s first visit to Redmond.</quote>
  <quote>Google is Jon Skeet behind a proxy.</quote>
  <quote>If anyone writes delete JonSkeet; in C, the Apocalypse will come.</quote>
  <quote>If Jon Skeet posts a duplicate question on StackOverflow, the original question will be closed as a duplicate.</quote>
  <quote>If the Internet is the web then Jon Skeet is the spider.</quote>
  <quote>If you have 10000 reputation points and Jon Skeet has 10000 reputation points, Jon Skeet has more reputation than you.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t answer questions on SO...he stares them down till they answer themselves.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet returned intellisense and got his money back!</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet took out Harry Callahan with an anonymous delegate before he could say &apos;do you punk?&apos;</quote>
  <quote>Jeff Atwood bought a monster GPU just to calculate Jon Skeets&apos;s rep on SO...CPUs don&apos;t cut it anymore.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can code in Perl and make it look like Java.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can divide by zero.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can make the Kessel run in under twelve parsecs.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can recite π. Backwards.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can solve the travelling salesman in O(1).</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can stop an infinite loop just by thinking about it.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet can throw an exception further than anyone else, and in less time.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet coded his last project entirely in Microsoft Paint, just for the challenge.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet codes only with final sealed methods. No one has ever needed to override any of Jon Skeet&apos;s code.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not &quot;Abort, Retry, Ignore&quot;. Ever.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not recognize anonymous types in .NET...he knows everyone of them and where they live.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not refer to himself in the third person. Jon Skeet is always the first person, regardless of who is speaking about him.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not run his programs. He just whispers &quot;you better run&quot;. And it runs.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not sleep...He waits.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not use exceptions when programming. He has not been able to identify any of his code that is not exceptional.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet does not use revision control software. None of his code has ever needed revision.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t call a background worker, background workers call Jon Skeet.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t have performance bottlenecks. He just makes the universe wait its turn.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t need a debugger, he just stares down the bug until the code confesses.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t need delegates, he does all the work himself.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t use #include. He thinks it&apos;s cheating.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet doesn&apos;t write books, the words assemble themselves out of fear.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet dreams in ones and zeros. When two shows up, it is a nightmare. But again that&apos;s only in theory. Two doesn&apos;t exist for Jon.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet has already written a book about C# 9.0. It’s currently sealed up. In three years, Anders Hejlsberg is going to open the book to see if the language design team got it right.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet has more &quot;Nice Answer&quot; badges than you have badges.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet has root access to your system.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet has the key to Open Source. He just doesn&apos;t want to close it.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet has written the best programming language. Its source has just one command... void JonSkeet();</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is *IntelliSense*.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is a BSOD in himself: Best Stack Overflow Definition.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is immutable. If something&apos;s going to change, it&apos;s going to have to be the rest of the universe.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is not close to perfection, perfection is close to Jon Skeet.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is the only person who has ranked higher than Jon Skeet in the SO all-time rep league.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is the only top 100 SO user who is human. The others are bots that he coded to pass the time between questions.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet is the traveling salesman. Only he knows the shortest route.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet knows the air speed velocity of an unladen swallow, both African and European.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet LINQs all things.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet once answered one of my questions 42 seconds before I asked it. It is my belief that he employed a super computer and Infinite Improbability Drive technology to achieve this result.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet once wrote an entire operating system in his sleep on a Treo with no battery, powered only by the force of his will.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet only solves NP-awesome problems.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet saved the Princess.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet took the red pill and the blue pill, and can phase-shift in and out of the Matrix at will.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet uses Visual Studio to burn CDs.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s addition operator doesn&apos;t commute; it teleports to where he needs it to be.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s brain thinks binary.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s code doesn&apos;t follow a coding convention. It is the coding convention.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s heart rate is 5 GHz.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s keyboard doesn&apos;t have F1 key, the computer asks for help from him.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s SO reputation is only as modest as it is because of integer overflow (SQL Server does not have a datatype large enough).</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s styling is connected to a CSS file.</quote>
  <quote>Jon Skeet&apos;s threads do not sleep. They wait.</quote>
  <quote>MSDN is a post-it Jon Skeet wrote when he was four.</quote>
  <quote>Nobody has EVER dared to close the &lt;JonSkeet&gt; tag.</quote>
  <quote>Norman Bates lives a normal life today...Jon Skeetfixed the unwanted callbacks and rewrote Mother.Dispose().</quote>
  <quote>Once Jon Skeet went to the library...Since then the library was dynamically linked.</quote>
  <quote>Seventh normal form (7NF) for database normalization IS Jon Skeet.</quote>
  <quote>The &apos;Jigsaw Killer&apos; didn&apos;t die of cancer...he died of heartbreak. JS kept leaving &apos;same time next week :)&apos; post-its in his traps.</quote>
  <quote>The Dining Philosophers wait while Jon Skeet eats.</quote>
  <quote>The only time Jon Skeet was wrong was when he thought he had made a mistake.</quote>
  <quote>There are two types of programmers: good programmers, and those that are not Jon Skeet.</quote>
  <quote>There is no &apos;CTRL&apos; button on Jon Skeet&apos;s computer. Jon Skeet is always in control.</quote>
  <quote>Users don&apos;t mark Jon Skeet&apos;s answers as accepted. The universe accepts them out of a sense of truth and justice.</quote>
  <quote>When a null reference exception goes to sleep, it checks under the bed for Jon Skeet.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet does a search on Google..the only result is &quot;I&apos;ll be right back&quot;.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet presses F5, the Garbage collector collects itself...there is no other garbage.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet is on a diet and doesn&apos;t eat fast food, all hard disks change from FAT to NTFS.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet is programming the Garbage Collector rests. The objects know when to destroy themselves.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet points to null, null quakes in fear.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet presses Ctrl+Alt+Delete, worldwide computers restart is initiated. The same goes for format.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet solves an equation the variables becomes constants.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet throws an exception, nothing can catch it.</quote>
  <quote>When Jon Skeet&apos;s code fails to compile the compiler apologises.</quote>
  <quote>When you search for &quot;guru&quot; on Google it says &quot;Did you mean Jon Skeet?&quot;</quote>
</quotes>